// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "Where is Nami College Located?",
  answer: "Gokarneshowr",
  options: [
    "Gokarneshowr",
    "Baneshwor",
    "Jorpati",
    "Budanilkantha"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: "Nami is partnered with which University?",
  answer: "Northhamption",
  options: [
    "Oxford",
    "Havard",
    "Stanford",
    "Northhamption"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: "Who is the principal of Nami College?",
  answer: "Sanjeev Udas",
  options: [
    "Ankit Thapa",
    "Nischal Khadka",
    "Devendra Timilsina",
    "Sanjeev Udas"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: "Who teaches web development for L4?",
  answer: "Ankit Sir",
  options: [
    "Ankit Sir",
    "Nischal Sir",
    "Bijayasri Maam",
    "Kumar Sir"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: "Who teaches networking for L4?",
  answer: "Nischal Sir",
  options: [
    "Bijayasri Maam",
    "Kumar Sir",
    "Nischal Sir",
    "Ankit Sir"
  ]
},

  {
  numb: 6,
  question: "Who teaches CS for L4?",
  answer: "Bijayasri Maam",
  options: [
    "Bijayasri Maam",
    "Kumar Sir",
    "Nischal Sir",
    "Ankit Sir"
  ]
},

  {
  numb: 7,
  question: "When was Nami College established?",
  answer: "2013",
  options: [
    "2017",
    "2009",
    "2015",
    "2013"
  ]
},

  {
  numb: 8,
  question: "Who is the Chairperson of NAMI college?",
  answer: "Arzu Rana Deuba",
  options: [
    "Devendra Timilsina",
    "Nick Petford",
    "Arzu Rana Deuba",
    "Sanjeev Udas"
  ]
},

  {
  numb: 9,
  question: "Who is the Head of Finance?",
  answer: "Pranil Pandey",
  options: [
    "Pranil Pandey",
    "Ram Bahadur Deuba",
    "Rejmee Rai",
    "Pragya Luitel"
  ]
},

  {
  numb: 10,
  question: "Who is the gardener of Nami College?",
  answer: "Hemnath Neupane",
  options: [
    "Pragya Khadka",
    "Hemnath Neupane",
    "Rajendra Nepal",
    "Bishwo Lamichhane"
  ]
},

  {
  numb: 11,
  question: "Who is the IT System Administrator?",
  answer: "Prajapati Acharya",
  options: [
    "Prajapati Pokhrel",
    "Prajapati Acharya",
    "Prajapati Ghimire",
    "Nirmal Timilsina"
  ]
},

 {
  numb: 12,
  question: "In which category did the college win award in 2017?",
  answer: "Best Rising College",
  options: [
    "Best Rising College",
    "Fastest Growing College",
    "Creative College Award",
    "Intercollge Speech Competition"
  ]
},

  {
  numb: 13,
  question: "Where is Nami College about to shift?",
  answer: "New Baneshwor",
  options: [
    "Old Baneshwor",
    "Sankhamul",
    "New Baneshwor",
    "Tinkune"
  ]
},

  {
  numb: 14,
  question: "Who is the Programme Leader of Management faculty?",
  answer: "Rohit Sharma",
  options: [
    "Pradeep Khadka",
    "Sandip Lamichhane",
    "Virat kohli",
    "Rohit Sharma"
  ]
},

  {
  numb: 15,
  question: "Who is the Module Leader of Environment Science?",
  answer: "Ranjana Maharjan",
  options: [
    "Nirmala Khatri",
    "Ram Bahadur Deuba",
    "Ranjana Maharjan",
    "Rejmee Rai"
  ]
},


];




// you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
// but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....
//   {
//   numb: 6,
//   question: "Your Question is Here",
//   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
//   options: [
//     "Option 1",
//     "option 2",
//     "option 3",
//     "option 4"
//   ]
// },
//];